Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - P-S
        - Ponderosa Twins Plus One - 2+2+1= Ponderosa Twins Plus One, 1971; SR-27299; Ponderosa Twins Plus One (Box 60)
          Horoscope Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Pop, Iggy - Kill city, 1977; SR-27300; Pop, Iggy; Williamson, James (Box 60)
          Catalog # BLP 4001; A-side Matrix # K-9348
          BOMP!
          Burbank, California
        - Porru, Miki - Mani; I ragazzi fanno il rap, 1990; SR-27301; Porru, Miki (Box 60)
          Catalog # SRLM 2098; A-side Matrix # SRLM 2098-1L 10390
          Ricordi
          Italy
        - Poser - Heavy action, 1987; SR-27302; Poser (Box 60)
          Catalog # GS2274; A-side Matrix # GS2274-A
        - Positive K - Step up front, 1988; SR-27303; Positive K (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27304. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 1229; A-side Matrix # STDM-55731-55732-1
          First Priority Music
        - Positive K - Step up front, 1988; SR-27304; Positive K (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27303. 2 copies.
        - Positive Mental Attitude - Ruff n' tuff; Spirits dancin', 1995; SR-27305; Positive Mental Attitude (Box 60)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # TI006; A-side Matrix # MPO T1006 A-1
          Tech Itch Recordings
          Bristol, United Kingdom
        - Positively Black - Think like ya enemy, 1988; SR-27306; Positively Black; Prince Kharique (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27307. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TR-158A; A-side Matrix # CSB TR 12"-158 A
          Trumpet Records
          Fanwood, New Jersey
        - Positively Black - Think like ya enemy, 1988; SR-27307; Positively Black; Prince Kharique (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27306. 2 copies.
        - Postmen - Documents (disc one), 1998; SR-27308; Postmen (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27309. Double album.
          Catalog # VVR1002311; A-side Matrix # 08 40433 20 2A1 V2VVR 1002311
          V2 Records
          Netherlands
        - Postmen - Documents (disc two), 1998; SR-27309; Postmen (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27308. Double album.
          Catalog # VVR1002311; A-side Matrix # 08 40433 20 1C1 V2VVR 1002311
        - Poussez! - Poussez!, 1979; SR-27310; Poussez! (Box 60)
          Catalog # VSD 79412; A-side Matrix # VSD 79412A-1C
          Vanguard
        - Poussez! - Come on and do it, 1979; SR-27311; Poussez! (Box 60)
          Catalog # SPV 25; A-side Matrix # SPV 25A-1B
        - Power - Play it again, Sam, 1981; SR-27312; Power (Box 60)
          Catalog # MAL 1204; A-side Matrix # MAL-1204-A-T1
          Malaco Records
          Jackson, Mississippi
        - Prayer Warriors - Unto the break, 1995; SR-27313; Prayer Warriors (Box 60)
          Catalog # SWL001; A-side Matrix # SWL-01-A
          Swell Records
          Scottsdale, Arizona
        - Prem-C - 5 senses of def, 2005; SR-27314; Prem-C (Box 60)
          Catalog # UAV002; A-side Matrix # UAV002-A-
          Underground Alliance
        - Presley, Elvis - C'mon everybody, 1975; SR-27315; Presley, Elvis (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27316. 2 copies. Different jacket
          Catalog # CAS-2518; A-side Matrix # CAS-2518-A 3 AM TP PA-8-1
          Pickwick
        - Presley, Elvis - C'mon everybody, 1975; SR-27316; Presley, Elvis (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27315. 2 copies. Different jacket
          Catalog # CAS-2518; A-side Matrix # CAS-2518-A TP PA 8-1
        - Preston, Billy - Pressin'on, 1982; SR-27317; Preston, Billy (Box 60)
          Catalog # 6020ML; A-side Matrix # 6020 MLA-15A S-L3 Z0J JS-KENDUN
        - Preston, Billy - A whole new thing, 1977; SR-27318; Preston, Billy (Box 60)
          Catalog # SP-5049; A-side Matrix # T2 SP-5049-T2
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Preston, Billy - Music from the motion picture "Fast Break", 1979; SR-27319; Preston, Billy; Syreeta (Box 60)
          Catalog # M7-915R1; A-side Matrix # TX M7-915-R1-A-
        - Preston, Billy - Just for you; Gigolette, 1981; SR-27320; Preston, Billy; Syreeta; Ozone (Box 60)
          Catalog # PR-85; A-side Matrix # PR 85A-66336-D/66336-DI-15B ZTK
        - Prince - Space, 1994; SR-27321; Prince (Box 60)
          Catalog # 0-41833; A-side Matrix # 0-41833 A REI-SRI
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Prince - Love symbol (disc one), 1992; SR-27322; Prince; New Power Generation; Prince and the New Power Generation (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27323. Double album.
          Catalog # 9362-45037-1; A-side Matrix # 936 245037-1-A
        - Prince - Love symbol (disc two), 1992; SR-27323; Prince; New Power Generation; Prince and the New Power Generation (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27322. Double album.
          Catalog # 9362-45037-1; A-side Matrix # 937 245037-1-C
        - Prince - Purple rain, 1984; SR-27324; Prince; Revolution; Prince and the Revolution (Box 60)
          Catalog # 925 110-1; A-side Matrix # 1-25110-A-SHI B-19421-SHI SLM 6851 1-2 R/S Alsdorf 925110-1 82
        - Prince - Royal mix, 1990; SR-27325; Prince (Box 60)
          Label obscured
          Catalog # PRM 91; A-side Matrix # PRM 91-A
          ON-Usound
        - Prince - Chocolate box (a superb collection of finest finished studio outtakes), 1987; SR-27326; Prince; Valentine (Box 60)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # PR-A; A-side Matrix # PR-A
          Sarotti Sound Products
          United States
        - Prince - You belong to Prince, 1981; SR-27327; Prince (Box 60)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # PH-A
          Prince
        - Prince - Clubbing it (disc one), 1988; SR-27328; Prince (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27329. Double album.
          Catalog # EX…009; A-side Matrix # ZZ 03 A 1
          Exit Records
        - Prince - Clubbing it (disc two), 1988; SR-27329; Prince (Box 60)
          In same jacket as # SR-27328. Double album.
          Catalog # EX…009; A-side Matrix # GWR 5 A 1
        - Prince - Dirty mind, 1980; SR-27330; Prince (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27331. Different discs.
          Catalog # BSK 3478; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3478 LW2
        - Prince - Head; Sister; Partyup, 1980; SR-27331; Prince (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27330. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-915; A-side Matrix # B-15388 PRO-A-915-A1
        - Prince - Stolen Treasure (disc one), 1991; SR-27332; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27333. Double album. Test pressing
          Catalog # GEM 001; A-side Matrix # PR-001-A-1
          Gemini Records
          Europe
        - Prince - Stolen Treasure (disc two), 1991; SR-27333; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27332. Double album. Test pressing
          Catalog # GEM 001; A-side Matrix # PR-002-A-1
        - Prince - Prince, 1979; SR-27334; Prince (Box 61)
          Catalog # BSK 3366; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3366 LW6
        - Prince - Musicology (disc one), 2004; SR-27335; Prince (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27336. Double album.
          Catalog # CK92560LP; A-side Matrix # CK 92560LP-A1
          Urban Division
        - Prince - Musicology (disc two), 2004; SR-27336; Prince (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27335. Double album.
          Catalog # CK92560LP; A-side Matrix # CK 92560LP-C1
        - Prince - By invitation only, 1988; SR-27337; Prince (Box 61)
          Catalog # CAMILLE 88; A-side Matrix # Z111-A1
          Camilleon Discs
        - Prince Charles and the City Beat Band - Stone killers, 1982; SR-27338; Prince Charles and the City Beat Band (Box 61)
          Catalog # V 2271; A-side Matrix # V-2271-A-2 TOWNHOUSE
          Virgin
        - Prince Charles and the City Beat Band - Combat zone, 1984; SR-27339; Prince Charles and the City Beat Band (Box 61)
          Catalog # 70246; A-side Matrix # M6 345625 2 70246-A
        - Prince Charles and the City Beat Band - We can make it happen, 1986; SR-27340; Prince Charles and the City Beat Band (Box 61)
          Catalog # 12P 348; A-side Matrix # 12P-345-A2 1 MT DAMONT
          PRT
        - Prince Jammy - Computerised dub, 1986; SR-27341; Prince Jammy (Box 61)
          Catalog # GREL 92; A-side Matrix # GREL 92 A1 PAG P2
          Greensleeves Records
        - Prisoners of Technology - Delikutt beats; What does it mean, 1997; SR-27342; Prisoners of Technology (Box 61)
          Catalog # FK04; A-side Matrix # MUSIC HOUSE FK04AA-1
          Fresh Kutt Records
        - Prisoners of Technology - Trick of technology (remix); Feeeeeeeel, 1997; SR-27343; Prisoners of Technology (Box 61)
          Catalog # FK001R; A-side Matrix # MUSIC HOUSE FK 01 A1 REMIX
        - Private, Gary - Private, 1981; SR-27344; Private, Gary (Box 61)
          Catalog # SEL 21608; A-side Matrix # SEL-21608-A-RE-1 STRAWBERRY FIELDS FOREVER
          Select Records
        - Prodigy - Breathe, 1996; SR-27345; Prodigy (Box 61)
          Catalog # XLT 80; A-side Matrix # XLT 80 A1 DAMONT MIKE'S -THE EXCHANGE Y
          XL Recordings
        - Professor Taub-Karcher - Die dunkelsequenz, 1997; SR-27346; Professor Taub-Karcher (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27347. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 511 661; A-side Matrix # 743 215 116 61-A1
          Loud & Slow
        - Professor Taub-Karcher - Die dunkelsequenz, 1997; SR-27347; Professor Taub-Karcher (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27346. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 511 661; A-side Matrix # 744 215 116 61-A1
        - Professor Griff and the Last Asiatic Disciples - Pawns in the game, 1990; SR-27348; Professor Griff and the Last Asiatic Disciples (Box 61)
          Catalog # XR-111; A-side Matrix # XR-111-A IN GOD We TRUST F5
          Luke SkyyWalker Records
          Liberty City, Florida
        - Propellerheads - Bang on!; Dive!, 1997; SR-27349; Propellerheads (Box 61)
          Catalog # WALL T 034; A-side Matrix # I SAY… DING DONG! WALL T 034 A1 SIMON -THE EXCHANGE
          Wall of Sound
        - Prophet, Michael - Blood stain, 1984; SR-27350; Prophet, Michael; Haynes, Michael; Wynter, N. (Box 61)
          Catalog # A 107; A-side Matrix # SBL 001-A
          Ashantites
          Riverdale, Maryland
        - Prophets of Da City - Universal souljaz, 1995; SR-21278; Prophets of Da City (Box 61)
          Catalog # NATLP54; A-side Matrix # NATLP 54 A
          Nation Records
        - Protector - Simply beautiful, 1984; SR-27351; Protector (Box 61)
          Catalog # PCR353; A-side Matrix # PCR-353A-RE1
        - Psychedelic Furs - Love my way, 1982; SR-27352; Psychedelic Furs (Box 61)
          Catalog # 44-03197; A-side Matrix # XSS 170331-1B
        - Public Enemy - There's a poison goin on… (disc one), 1999; SR-27353; Public Enemy (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27354. Double album.
          Catalog # 940.0004.12; A-side Matrix # B924407-01 A1 MK
          [PIAS] Recordings
        - Public Enemy - There's a poison goin on… (disc two), 1999; SR-27354; Public Enemy (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27353. Double album.
          Catalog # 940.0004.12; A-side Matrix # B924407-02 C1 MK
        - Puff Daddy and the Family - No way out (disc one), 1997; SR-27355; Puff Daddy and the Family; Puff Daddy; Diddy (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27356. Double album.
          Catalog # 78612-73012-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-73012-1-SA
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - Puff Daddy and the Family - No way out (disc two), 1997; SR-27356; Puff Daddy and the Family; Puff Daddy; Diddy (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27355. Double album.
          Catalog # 78612-73012-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-73012-1-SC
        - Puff Daddy - Do you like it….do you want it…., 1999; SR-27357; Puff Daddy; Diddy (Box 61)
          Catalog # BBDP-9245; A-side Matrix # BBDP 9245 SA
        - Pulsallama - The devil lives in my husband's body, 1982; SR-27358; Pulsallama (Box 61)
          Catalog # 12Y USA 2; A-side Matrix # A-1 12''-Y-USA-2-T
          Y America
        - Pure Energy - Party on, 1980; SR-27359; Pure Energy (Box 61)
          Catalog # DJ-404; A-side Matrix # PDS-404-A
          Prism
        - Q - Q, 1982; SR-27360; Q; St. James, Jon; Van Patten, Daniel R. (Box 61)
          Catalog # MAOX 1002; A-side Matrix # MOON AGE OBSESSION MAOX 1002 JS-KENDUN
          M.A.O. Records
        - Q-Project - Trouble; Daylight, 2001; SR-21279; Q-Project (Box 61)
          Catalog # ADVR002; A-side Matrix # ADVR-002-A
          Advance//d Recordings
        - Quad City All Star Christmas - All star Christmas (disc one), 1996; SR-27361; Quad City All Star Christmas (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27362. Double album.
          Catalog # 82970-1; A-side Matrix # F/W RCE STBB-960947-A
        - Quad City All Star Christmas - All star Christmas (disc two), 1996; SR-27362; Quad City All Star Christmas (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27361. Double album.
          Catalog # 82970-1; A-side Matrix # F/W RCE STBB-960949-A
        - Quannum - Solesides greatest bumps, 2000; SR-27363; Quannum (Box 61)
          Catalog # QP222-1; A-side Matrix # VINYL ONE QP22-1A CUT-TT-Hit Factory NYC
          Quannum Projects
        - Quansah, Eddie - Awo awo, 1979; SR-27364; Quansah, Eddie; Sadkin, Alex (Box 61)
          Catalog # MLPS-9546; A-side Matrix # STERLING A-1 MPLS-9546-A
        - Quatre Étoiles - 6 tubes; 6 hits, 1987; SR-27365; Quatre Étoiles (Box 61)
          Catalog # SYL8736; A-side Matrix # Y-D 87-5 8330 A EXP 8736
          Syllart Production
        - Quatro, Michael - Bottom line, 1981; SR-27366; Quatro, Michael (Box 61)
          Catalog # SW-70003; A-side Matrix # SPRO1-00013-A-(DJ) HI Criteria MF
          Spector Records International
          Coral Gables, Florida
        - Queen - Live killers (disc one), 1979; SR-27367; Queen (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27368. Double album.
          Catalog # 166 62792/93; A-side Matrix # DISCO-1-E-166-62792-A-1
          EMI
        - Queen - Live killers (disc two), 1979; SR-27368; Queen (Box 61)
          In same jacket as # SR-27367. Double album.
          Catalog # 167 62792/93; A-side Matrix # DISCO-2-E 166-62793-A-2
        - Queen - Hot space, 1982; SR-27369; Queen (Box 61)
          Catalog # E1-60128; A-side Matrix # E1-60128-A-7 SP 2SM1-4
        - Queen - The works, 1984; SR-27370; Queen (Box 61)
          Catalog # ST-12322; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12322-Z4 #2
        - Queen Samantha - The letter, 1978; SR-27371; Queen Samantha (Box 61)
          Catalog # ABL.17032; A-side Matrix # ABL-17032A-15 1A T G D
          Able Records
          Quebec, Canada
        - Quinta Faccia - Let em in, 1977; SR-27372; Quinta Faccia (Box 61)
          Catalog # 5094/010; A-side Matrix # 5094/010 A
          Universal International Music
        - R-Damski - Lord, 1996; SR-27373; R-Damski (Box 61)
          Catalog # OVER-X-PO 04; A-side Matrix # OVER-X-8O 04 A SST 45 UPM
          Over-X-Posure
        - R-Kidz - Dirty plate, 1998; SR-27374; R-Kidz (Box 61)
          Catalog # HAND048 T; A-side Matrix # HAND048 T A-1-1-
          Hard Hands
        - Radiance - Pick-n-choose, 1985; SR-27375; Radiance (Box 61)
          Catalog # 1-25153; A-side Matrix # SLM 7857 1-1 1-25153A-SH1 & B-20008-SH
          Qwest Records
        - Raekwon - Live from New York; Power, 1999; SR-27376; Raekwon (Box 61)
          Catalog # RPROLP4315; A-side Matrix # MB RPROLP-4315 A
          Loud Records
        - Raes - Dancing up a storm, 1979; SR-27377; Raes (Box 61)
          Catalog # SP-4754; A-side Matrix # SP-5245-M2 MR 24108 Z
        - Raheem - The vigilante, 1988; SR-27379; Raheem (Box 61)
          Catalog # SP-5212; A-side Matrix # SP-5212-A E52 -EMW-
        - Rahmlee - Heartbreaker, 1981; SR-27380; Rahmlee; Gant, Dean; Penovich, M. (Box 61)
          Catalog # HF-L-33-1031; A-side Matrix # HF-L-33-1031 S-8620
          Headfirst
        - Ram Jam - Portrait of the artist as a young ram, 1978; SR-27382; Ram Jam (Box 61)
          Catalog # JE 35287; A-side Matrix # P AL 35287-1D
          Epic
        - Rance Allen Group - The way it is, 1979; SR-27383; Rance Allen Group (Box 61)
          Catalog # ST-11994; A-side Matrix # ST-1-11994 G-2 wayn
        - Rankin Don - Piranha, 1991; SR-27384; Rankin Don; Dobson, Dobby (Box 61)
          Catalog # GA 106; A-side Matrix # GA 106-A PIRANHA
          Gyasi
        - Rankin, Louie - The muscle, 1992; SR-27385; Rankin, Louie (Box 61)
          Catalog # 1PRO 9040; A-side Matrix # S-27400 1PRO 9040 Hip Hop Mix
          Mesa Recordings
        - Ranking Joe - Natty superstar, 1980; SR-27386; Ranking Joe (Box 61)
          Catalog # JGML 6035; A-side Matrix # JGML-6035-A K Kmas Tering
          Joe Gibbs Music
        - Ranks, Cutty - 4 song sampler, 1996; SR-27387; Ranks, Cutty (Box 62)
          Catalog # SPRO 30119; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30119-A KM S-34512
          Priority Records
        - Ranks, Shabba - Rough & ready- Volume II, 1993; SR-27388; Ranks, Shabba (Box 62)
          Catalog # E 57203; A-side Matrix # AL 57203
        - Ranks, Tiger - Party with me, 1999; SR-27389; Ranks, Tiger; DJ A.P. (Box 62)
          Catalog # AV92; A-side Matrix # AV-92-A-RE1 F/W GSV
          AV8
        - Rappers' Convention - Rappers' Convention, 1986; SR-27390; Rappers' Convention (Box 62)
          Catalog # ST-17225; A-side Matrix # ST-1-17225-Z4 1-1
        - Rare Earth - Ma, 1973; SR-27391; Rare Earth; Whitfield, Norman (Box 62)
          Catalog # R 546L; A-side Matrix # R 546L-C5R5-7582-1 01B
          Rare Earth
        - Rare Essence - Disco fever; Huff & puff, 1978; SR-27392; Rare Essence (Box 62)
          Catalog # MG 505-ASI; A-side Matrix # MG-505-AD-1
          Major Records
        - Rare Essence - Body moves, 1982; SR-27393; Rare Essence (Box 62)
          Catalog # D-205; A-side Matrix # D-205-A F/W NS
        - Rare Essence - RE-2000 (disc one), 1999; SR-27394; Rare Essence (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27395, SR-27396. Double album. No entry on Discogs.
          Catalog # RE-2001; A-side Matrix # RE-2001-1-A EURODA DISK Dmm NY USA 39769 G
          Rare One Records
        - Rare Essence - RE-2000 (disc two), 1999; SR-27395; Rare Essence (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27394, SR-27396. Double album. No entry on Discogs.
          Catalog # RE-2001; A-side Matrix # RE-2001-1-C EURODA DISK Dmm NY USA 39771 G
        - Rare Essence - RE-2000 (disc two), 1999; SR-27396; Rare Essence (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27395, SR-27396. 2 copies. No entry on Discogs.
        - Rare Essence - Disco fever; Huff & puff, 1979; SR-27397; Rare Essence (Box 62)
          Catalog # DSKO 157; A-side Matrix # ST-D5K0-36610-1
        - Rastus - Steamin', 1972; SR-27398; Rastus (Box 62)
          Catalog # NRS-47003-A; A-side Matrix # NRS-47003-A-2-1-1 1 WINN PR
          Neighborhood Records
        - Ratzer, Karl - Street talk, 1979; SR-27399; Ratzer, Karl (Box 62)
          Catalog # VSD 79423; A-side Matrix # V SD79423A-1B
        - Raw Silk - Do it to the music, 1982; SR-27400; Raw Silk (Box 62)
          Catalog # WES 22148; A-side Matrix # B- WES-22148A-70527-2A
          West End Records
        - Raw Stylus - Believe in me, 1996; SR-27401; Raw Stylus (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27402. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RAWS 13; A-side Matrix # RAWS-13 A1
          Wired Recordings
        - Raw Stylus - Believe in me, 1996; SR-27402; Raw Stylus (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27401. 2 copies.
        - Ray, Goodman & Brown II - Ray, Goodman & Brown II, 1980; SR-27403; Ray, Goodman & Brown II (Box 62)
          Catalog # PD-1-6299; A-side Matrix # PD 1-6299-AS-SP 1-34M1-1
        - RCR - Give it to you, 1980; SR-27404; RCR; Rhodes, Chalmers & Rhodes (Box 62)
          Catalog # GS 111; A-side Matrix # GS-111-A MF
          Radio Records
          Ft. Lauderdale, Florida
        - Ready For The World - Ready For The World, 1985; SR-27405; Ready For The World (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27406. Different discs.
          Catalog # MCA-5594; A-side Matrix # MCA-4474-FDS-5 FUTURE DISC
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Ready For The World - Oh Sheila, 1985; SR-27406; Ready For The World (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27405. Different discs.
          Catalog # L33-17013; A-side Matrix # MCA-4610-FDS-1
        - Ready For The World - Ruff n' ready, 1988; SR-27407; Ready For The World (Box 62)
          Catalog # MCA-42198; A-side Matrix # MCA-7858-FDS-6 FUTURE DISC
        - Ready For The World - Long time coming, 1986; SR-27408; Ready For The World (Box 62)
          Catalog # MCA-5829; A-side Matrix # MCA 5946 FDS-3 FUTURE DISC
        - Real - Debbie does Deptford, 2000; SR-27409; Real (Box 62)
          Catalog # EUHO 026-6; A-side Matrix # 08 43891 20 1A1 EUHO 026-6
          Eukahouse
        - Real Lyphe - What you want (Que tu quieres?), 1999; SR-27410; Real Lyphe; Papoose; Trigger The Gambler (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27411. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AV90; A-side Matrix # AV-90-A F/W GSV
        - Real Lyphe - What you want (Que tu quieres?), 1999; SR-27411; Real Lyphe; Papoose; Trigger The Gambler (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27410. 2 copies.
        - Real Thing - Groovy freaks, 1981; SR-27412; Real Thing (Box 62)
          Catalog # 4Z8 01063; A-side Matrix # 4Z8-01063-4AA
          Believe In A Dream
          Washington, D.C.
        - Real Thing - Can you feel the force?, 1978; SR-27413; Real Thing (Box 62)
          Catalog # 28-50689; A-side Matrix # XSS-165492-1B
        - Record, Eugene - I don't mind; Take everything, 1979; SR-27414; Record, Eugene (Box 62)
          Catalog # WBSD 8845; A-side Matrix # WBSD-8845-WIL-0357-VI-S-M3 24358 (4)
        - Record, Eugene - Trying to get to you, 1978; SR-27415; Record, Eugene (Box 62)
          Catalog # BSK 3097; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3097 LW2
        - Red Fox - Tek hood; Tek more, 1999; SR-27416; Red Fox; Denice The Menace (Box 62)
          Catalog # VPRT058; A-side Matrix # VPRT 058-A TEK HOOD PAUL-VD
          Joe Frasier
          Jamaica, New York
        - Red Hot Chili Peppers - The uplift mofo party plan, 1987; SR-27417; Red Hot Chili Peppers (Box 62)
          Catalog # ELT-48036; A-side Matrix # ELT-1-48036-Z1 DMM MASTERDISK DMM SP1-3
        - Red Snapper - Making bones (disc one), 1998; SR-27418; Red Snapper (Box 62)
          Catalog # WARPLP56; A-side Matrix # WARPLP 56 A-01-1-
          Warp Records
        - Red Snapper - The sleepless, 1998; SR-27419; Red Snapper (Box 62)
          Catalog # WAP108; A-side Matrix # WAP 108 A-01-1- F-A- TOWNHOUSE
        - Redd - It's Redd, 1986; SR-27420; Redd (Box 62)
          Catalog # AFL1-5900; A-side Matrix # 1-2 A 2 13788 AFL1-5900 A-3 BMM
          RCA
        - Redd, Sharon - You got my love; Can you handle it, 1981; SR-27421; Redd, Sharon (Box 62)
          Catalog # PRL D 611-AS; A-side Matrix # PRLD-611-A HERb FK
          Prelude Records
        - Redd, Sharon - Sharon Redd, 1980; SR-27422; Redd, Sharon (Box 62)
          Catalog # PRL 12181 AS; A-side Matrix # P RL-12181 AS-1E
        - Redding, Otis - The best of Otis Redding, 1980; SR-27423; Redding, Otis (Box 62)
          Catalog # ATL 50752; A-side Matrix # WEA 50752-A PF
        - Reddings - If looks could kill, 1985; SR-27424; Reddings (Box 62)
          Catalog # 422-823 324-1 Y-1; A-side Matrix # 422823 324-1-AS-ALD B-20784-A-D SLM 8994 1-1
        - Reddings - Class (is what you got), 1981; SR-27425; Reddings (Box 62)
          In same jacket as # SR-27426, SR-27427
          Catalog # AS 1287; A-side Matrix # XSM168779-A